Here we go... Upokami!
This time, my partner is Angelem's Tameshigashi Ondo!
This is Miku Nishizaki from Ocha no Ma!
This show is about the behind-the-scenes production of various artists belonging to the up-front group.
This is a program that goes behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
our recordings and rehearsals.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
So let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I'm Ei Tamura.
I'm Ei Tamura, and I'm talking about the dance rehearsal we recently had at Angulum.
We had to shoot a video for reference at the end of the dance rehearsal, so we had to do it all at once.
I don't usually do that.
We usually don't do that, but at that time, we all got together and got the engine going.
We were all fired up and ready to go for it.
And then Ms. Sasaki started to cry.
Tears.
I don't know what was really going on, I don't know.
I don't know, but I think I felt
I think I felt a little bit of youthfulness or togetherness at that time.
I think they were happy tears because they felt a sense of youth or togetherness and that made them happy.
I think that's what made him happy, and I think that's why he cried.
When we were filming the video, I was holding back my tears.
When we shot the video, we had to hold back our tears while we shot the video.
It was a good memory.
It's a very nice story.
Thank you very much.
I, Miku Sasaki, would like to talk about how much I like recording these days.
Yes, I did.
When I was recording, I was allowed to sit in the seat where the engineer usually sits.
I was able to experience a different musical environment there than when I was recording.
I realized once again how much I love music, and I could hear so many wonderful and beautiful sounds.
I could hear so many wonderful and beautiful sounds.
So I had an epiphany that maybe I love recording the most.
I'm sure we'll be doing a lot more recording in the future.
I'm looking forward to it and I'm excited about it!
That's nice. Great.
I'm sure you'll learn a lot from the recording, but let's keep up the good work!
Yes, I'll do my best.
Now, let's start with this video.
Tsubaki Factory new member lesson video
Please take a look at the lesson of the three new members who joined Tsubaki Factory.
This is the end of the Tsubaki Factory video.
The most difficult one in my opinion is Suzuki of Power Flower and Jimzaki
Then what was the most difficult for you?
Jim Zaki's Suzuki
Power Flower
So today, I would like to practice the rhythm of the song, and I'm sure you have memorized the choreography of the song, but I'm sure you've already woken me up, so let's start with the basic rhythm of the song.
I'm sure you've memorized the choreography of the song, but I'm sure you've already made it up, so I'd be happy if we can combine the basic rhythm of the song and how to sing it.
It's okay if you make mistakes in the lyrics, because this is not a singing lesson, so please practice singing by moving your mouth.
Please take the microphone with you and sing all the songs today.
Walk normally.
One, two.
Yes, quickly sing in your own face.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
2010, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20
2013, Week 1, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30
2013, 24, 25, 36, 37, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 45, 46 , 47, 48, 49, 50
First, listen to the sound properly.
Take the sound and get the rhythm.
If you don't listen to the sound
Just do what you're told to do.
What are you doing?
You don't know what you are doing. So listen to the sound carefully, listen carefully yourself, and listen to the sound properly. Then, think of it as putting your body on the thing that is making the sound and making the sound come true.
Okay, let's go one more time. Let's try one more time. Can I try it this time while dancing?
I'm always late with excuses and it's your fault.
Come on, let's do it again.
Thank you, that's what happens when I'm sorry.
Another one of this someone's work might forgive me.
You're so full of shit, it's easy!
Singing, bible, love, show it to me
I'll squeal and squeal and squeal in that greed
Save my knowledge
Protect me, protect me, protect me, protect me Protect me and my knowledge.
I'll run away.
No one can be kind to me
Because no one knows and no one will know
It's me.
More!
The basic rhythm has always been 16.
Love is now when it wants to be loved.
If the heel falls off, the weight goes down.
Love needs love now.
Keep your heels up.
It's like a regular poor youth.
So let's tighten up your hips and your stomach
I want to sing
Sing it while you dance, okay?
Five, six, seino
Seven, Seiman.
Eight, Ceyman.
Nine. Ceyman.
Yes!
He wants love.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Love is for wanting to stop properly now
Love is now, I'm flying a great member
But if "love is now," you can't sing.
So I want you to be conscious of stopping properly
Love now, love more
This place will never lose its gravity.
I'm looking for love.
Don't be lazy
Just pretend you've learned it left and right.
And if you go, the middle of the body is
The middle of the body is covered, so it's in this state.
I want you to make sure it comes out the other side.
But I don't want them to come out together.
So we're going to go straight up, and then we're going to let the body go.
Ready, dun, dun, dun. Okay, Dan. Dan.
Okay, one more time.
Did you see his face?
Ready, go, go, dah-dah-dah.
The sound is like, "Ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong.
Imagine that. Ready, go!
Bubba, that's good.
That's why I want you to do that movement, even if you're doing it alone.
I want you to imagine that.
It's important to get the rhythm by yourself. It's important to get the sound and the choreography in sync.
And it's important to speak out, even if you make a mistake in the song already
And be aware of the microphone hold.
Yes, please!
Seriousness all around, dang dang dang dang
Make them sing, make them love you, show them love
Use that power, use that power, cue it up
I'm a stain, I'll run away
Because kindness is not a melon
Try it, I'm happy, it's a testimony
I'm a testimony, I'm a testimony
I'm looking for love
I want love now, I want love now, I want love now, I want love now
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
Love, love, love, love
Thank you for watching.
Ladies and gentlemen, the microphone hold is weak.
Yes, yes, yes.
If I write it like this, the microphone won't ring.
Try to hold the mic as straight as you can.
Straight up.
Well, not straight, but...
It's a very limited spot.
So the mic won't be able to hear your voice.
You were so good at this.
The way he held the mic was really good.
If you hold it that way, your voice will definitely come in.
Thank you very much.
Let's get into the habit of holding it here just before you sing. Make a habit of always bringing it here a little before you sing.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll see you next time.
If you do whatever you have to do.
Thank you very much.
Someday, Teri Teri Teri
M tomato
Yours, Essa
damaged
Not me.
I'm having a hard time sleeping.
Wait a minute.
Mmm.
me
Today, Mr. Kasai and Ms. Mitsuhashi taught me the details of the song in a very gentle way, and it was very easy to understand.
I want to practice it again and again at home so that I can perfect it,
I have been learning it as it is,
I had learned to dance with 16 beats or something like that,
I learned how to dance with 16 beats, and how to stop the dance,
I want to do that more at home,
I would like to work on that more at home.
I am not good at rhythm, so I struggled a lot,
I struggled a lot with rhythm, but when I practiced dancing at home, I tried to be more conscious of rhythm,
I will be more conscious of the rhythm when I practice dancing at home.
I want to do my best to express my unique movements and expressions in the parts where there are no choreographies and in the parts where there are choreographies.
I want to do my best to express myself in the parts where there are no choreographies and in the parts where there are choreographies.
The three new members are absorbing very quickly,
I was impressed by how quickly the three new members absorbed what I said and how quickly they were able to do what I said,
I also thought that I would like to do my best again,
I hope we can have another dance lesson together.
Everyone worked so hard. They were amazing. It was amazing.
When I joined as a new member, we had a period like this where we practiced Kisso every day and learned Angstrom's songs,
It reminded me of that. I remember that time. I have the videos of those days, and sometimes I want to look back at them and wonder why I was so bad at dancing.
When I look back at them, I wonder why I was so bad at dancing.
I think that time was really necessary for me,
I think it was really necessary for me.
I was so nervous that I couldn't even think about the stretches.
I was so nervous that I couldn't even think about the stretches. I was so nervous. I was so nervous.
I remember that time very well, and even though I knew it in my head, I could not move my body at that time. So the images really conveyed how hard I was working.
I really appreciate your hard work. I really appreciate your hard work.
It was amazing.
I hope they will continue to work hard.
I hope they will continue to do their best.
Keep up the good work and keep up the good work.
This is the video of the lesson for new members of Sobaiki Factory.
I'm sure it will be good for you.
Next, here is a video of Ami Tanimoto and Masato Fukuda's dance lecture. Dance lecture by Ami Tanimoto and Masato Fukuda.
In this corner, they lecture the choreography of the choruses of songs other than single songs.
Let's take a look.
This is Ami Tanimoto of Tsubaki Factory and Masato Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory.
Now, this time, I'd like to give you a lecture on the choreography of the choruses of Tsubaki Factory's non-single songs.
This time, I would like to give you a lecture on the choreography of the chorus of the song "Stay Free & Stay Tune", which is a new song from Tsubaki Factory's third album "Third Moment".
This song is a song that is really popular at live performances, and there are parts where you can sing along with the audience, and there is a lot of impressive choreography.
The choreography is also a bit impressive, so I chose this song with the hope that everyone will be able to dance to the chorus.
So, we would like to dance as a model for you.
Thank you for watching.
Let's get more aggressive!
Now, I would like to give you a lecture.
I would like to give you a lecture on the chorus.
Before the chorus, there is a little preparation choreography.
Before the chorus, there is a little choreography like a preparation.
It's like tapping something.
Bend down a little bit.
Tap, tap, tap, tap.
Yes, I'm going to hit it.
And then
Stay free, and it's like a beam.
It's called "Pilapilapillar".
Then, on par.
Pillapillar
I'm satisfied.
It's like a suspension strap.
Our dance teacher used to teach us how to use them.
I'm holding on to the strap of the train.
like you're holding on to the train's strap. It's like I'm holding on to it.
I'm satisfied.
Don't.
Don't
I feel like I shouldn't.
It's difficult, isn't it?
When you shouldn't be satisfied
I'd like you to make a batten mark with both hands.
The foot that comes out is from this side.
I don't know if you call it the back leg.
Bend your left leg first.
I feel like I shouldn't be dead.
Bring it from the waist under the chin.
You'll feel better.
Together.
I feel like you're drawing a little bit of a half circle from the bottom, and then you're going to raise it up at an angle, and then you're going to put your index finger out.
Point to it.
And then, "together", "twice", "thump", "thump".
Tap, tap, tap, tap.
Together, go around once without looking yet.
With your left foot on the axis, go around the world.
Go around.
Let's go out to the world
Raise your elbows like this.
Go, go, go
From the side
It looks like this.
There are two of them, actually.
But this one is a little easier to understand.
Let's go out.
Let's do it.
Next time, we'll start with the forward-facing one.
Now we're going to do it sideways.
Stay tuned.
Go home.
Do you understand?
Do you understand? Knock-knock.
I was doing the thump-thump-thump over here. Earlier I was doing the thump-thump-thump over here.
Tonton-tonton-tonton in the opposite direction.
What not to change
is this one, pointing and tapping twice.
Don't change it.
It's a hugging gesture.
Cu-cu-cu-cu with both hands.
Embrace.
Jump three times.
Tilt your head slightly to this side.
And finally, stand up.
Let's keep changing.
From the middle of the song, right?
There is a choreographed fist pump.
This is choreographed in the image of
This is choreographed to resemble the image of a "gut touch".
So on the third time, everyone puts their fists forward like this.
So it's a choreography that you can do together with the fans.
So the choreography will be like "Goo-touch" with the fans.
For each of the third times, everyone is free to play gutatch with someone else.
It would be nice if the fans could do a little bit with each other.
Maybe the members also do it in front of the audience at live performances.
I'd like to think of it as a "goo-touch" rather than a "punch" at that time.
We'd be happy if you fans could do this too!
Please subscribe to our channel!
When you play "jaja jaja jaja jaja jaja jaja jaja jaja jaja jaja jaja jaja jaja", you'll see this pose which is very impressive in this song.
Is it a meow called "Gao"?
Then, you hold your right hand like a meow, and then you say, "I have to go," and then you scratch your right hand in front of you.
Then you cross your right hand with "I have to go.
Oh!
Lift your legs a little. How's that? It may be quite difficult.
But once you learn it, it's easy to do. Especially the punching gesture at the end.
Especially the punching gesture at the end and the "gao" gesture are easy to do, so I hope everyone will try to imitate them.
Let's dance together!
Stay free!
I feel like I shouldn't be alone.
Let's go out together to the world we have not yet seen
Let's go out together, youthLet's go out, youth
Let's hold on to what we mustn't change
Let's keep changing
Fight Fight Fight Fight
Let's go on the offensive even more
How was it?
I think it was a little difficult.
We struggled a lot when we were putting the choreography together.
We struggled a lot with the choreography, but as we did it over and over again, I thought it was really fun to perform.
I think it's fun to perform.
I hope everyone will learn it.
I'd like you to learn this one and this fist pump.
I want to do this with everyone.
I want to do the "Goo-touch".
I want everyone to learn the choreography.
I'd like you all to learn the choreography, so I'd be very happy if you could watch a lot of videos and learn the choreography.
I'm counting on you!
That's all for now, Ami Tanimoto and Mari Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory
and Mari Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory.
Bye bye!
From my point of view, I thought there were a lot of cute choreographies.
and the choreography that goes along with the lyrics...
I don't know if it's Minami from "Gao Gao" at the end
I'm not sure if she's the Minami of Gao Gao at the end, but there were some really cute poses.
I would love to do the "Goo Touch" and so on.
If you recycle the lyrics like this
I think it will be easier for everyone to imitate at concerts and other events.
I, as a member of Hello Project
I think it would be great to have a video lecture on dance
I would like to be able to perform this song at a Hello Project concert.
I would be very grateful if I had a lecture video of this song at a Hello Project concert
I would be very grateful if I could watch the video and learn it over and over again.
I'm going to watch it again and again to learn it.
That's all for the dance lecture by Ami Tanimoto and Mari Fukuda!
Let's work hard together!
Next up is the next episode of Apkami with Shion Tamenaga of Angulum and Miku Nishizaki of Ochanomimi!
JuiceJuice Wonderful World 2023 JuiceJuice Ver. Bark Recording
Here's a look at the vocal recording of JuiceJuice's latest album, Wonderful World 2023 JuiceJuice Ver. by Ichika Arisawa! Wonderful World 2023 JuiceJuice Ver. from JuiceJuice's latest album. Watch Ichika Arisawa's Vocal Recording!
Okay, let's do it.
I'm going to tsurugi out the chorus, so please sing the part you're going to sing.
Well, after all, the second one is Cabina Bo Advis Bokun by Kei Suzuki Current
and if it's Masako ZAD, then isf he really does it
It was a rip.
I don't know.
I don't know... están.
During the journey, the earth is illuminated
Life is fine.
You're really copying me right now.
What? You're copying me?
No, I'm not?
I think that's what happens when you sing in an easy voice.
I see.
I can already see it, but that's okay.
You can say that too.
Okay, I'll take another one.
It was something I couldn't reach
Now that I've met you
This world is beautiful, isn't it?
If I could have met you
I'd light up the earth
Life is
It's a beautiful day
You say love me
From the place
You and me.
Let's go for it!
Life is
You stay absentee
me
lalala...
It's for both of us Two things.
In terms of pitch, let's say, well, you know, I'm getting a la la la la la la, so, yes.
Normally, you should be holding the meteoric lauvin. I'm sorry, I got upset.
Let's do it again. Please do.
Meteor shower is clear.
You say love me, and I say love you
Forever and ever only you
The song belongs to both of us
You say love me, and I say love you
Please do
Life is fine
La la la la, You Say Love Me
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Then I'll do the door ball.
Door ball, yes.
Isn't this world wonderful
What great love I'm surrounded by
When I'm with you
When I think of you
That's all I need
It's a Wonderful World
More
Well, it's like this world belongs to both of us.
Oh, okay.
Okay, let's do it.
Please do.
This world is
Isn't it wonderful?
What great love we have here.
When I have you
When I think of you
It's a Wonderful World
Okay, okay!
Thank you very much.
She sang in a way that made me feel like I was having a great time listening to her.
She even played the violin in the middle of the song, which really created a sense of enjoying the music.
I could really feel how she was riding on the sound, and it was really nice to listen to.
This is the vocal recording of JuiceJuice Wonderful World 2023 JuiceJuice Ver. This is the vocal recording of JuiceJuice Wonderful World 2023 JuiceJuice Ver. Arisawa Ichika.
Thank you for watching.
Thanks again for all your hard work.
It's time to say goodbye to the cardboard that Tameshigashi Ondo Nishizaki has made so much of.
I have been watching various videos, but the main focus for me is Ichika Arisawa's vocals.
I was very impressed with her vocals during the recording session... and the way she played the viba violin.
She looked so happy and excited that I was thrilled to see her playing the violin.
It was a recording aid, so I was so excited to see her playing the violin.
I wanted to give meaning to the ring so that I could open the violin as well as Ande did.
I was really impressed with the dance lecture.
I was really impressed with the dance lecture, and I was also looking at the details of the dance lecture.
I was looking at the details like holding the microphone with her left hand...
I think it's my personal favorite that he holds the microphone with his left hand because he often performs songs other than the singles at the concert.
I personally like to see that kind of hand holding the microphone, and I wanted everyone to see it, so that they can learn the dance moves and see them.
In this episode, we're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally get to see.
This time, we'll be talking with Shion Tamenaga of Angulum and Miku Nishizaki of Ocha-no-Ma.
and Miku Nishizaki of Ochanoma.
Good bye!
What's next on Apkami?
Inaba Manaka Overwhelming Love! The making of the music video shoot
And
Tsubaki Factory's latest album
The recording of the third moment will be released!
Enjoy!
Thank you for watching!